<ModMetaData>
	<name>iflyBayonet</name>
	<author>ifly6</author>
    <packageId>ifly6.iflyBayonet</packageId>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.3</li>
		<li>1.4</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<description>
v0.5.3. This is a public alpha. I make no assurances that there are no major bugs. Please report any bugs at https://github.com/ifly6/iflyBayonet.		

Adds a belt-equippable bayonet which attaches to bayonet-compatible weapons automatically without needing to create a whole new gun. Those bayonets can then be used in melee combat (if also equipping a compatible bayonet-luggable ranged weapon). Bayonets cannot be used alone; an invisible force holds them to the belt.

For the technically minded, the mod specifically changes the bayonet-compatible weapon's "poke" melee attacks. It leaves other weapon types, like bashing with a stock, in, replacing any time a bayonet-compatible weapon pokes with a bayonet stab.

This mod also patches the average melee damage calculation and battle log to report use of the bayonet. It also creates an alert if a pawn equips a bayonet belt without also having a compatible weapon. If your pawns are equipping the belt willy-nilly and you don't like this, change your Apparel rules in Assign.

Bayonets are created at the smithing table and have most of their statistics taken from a combination of knives and spears. The cost is a bit more expensive than a knife (the model of the bayonet is that of a 1907 SMLE bayonet with quillion) and the damage is a bit less than a spear, being a bit more clunky.

Please report errors in 1.4. Preliminary tests were done to ensure that bayonet patching still works.
	</description>
	<url>https://steamcommunity.com/id/ifly6/myworkshopfiles/?appid=294100</url>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
</ModMetaData>